[{
    "category": {
        "نظم الجزء الاول": {
            "one": {
                "question": "هي الافكار المنطقيه المتتابعه لمجال معين يمكن تعميمه لي كافة المجالات ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "جوده المعلومات",
                    "answer_2": "المنظمه",
                    "answer_3": "الجمعيه العامه للنظم",
                    "correct_answer": "لنظريه العامه لنظم"
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "هو مجموعة من الاجزاء التي ترتبط بعضها مع بعض لتحقيق هدف معين ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "المنظمه",
                    "answer_2": "نظم المعلومات الاداريه",
                    "answer_3": "وظيفه المعالجه",
                    "correct_answer": "النظام"
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "وظيفه المعالجه هي التي تعمل علي تعديل وتخزين البيانات لاجراء عمليات",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "جميع الاجابات صحيحه",
                    "answer_2": "منطقيه",
                    "answer_3": "حسابيه فقط",
                    "correct_answer": "حسابيه ومنطقيه"
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": " من مكونات النظام كل مايلي ماعدا",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "البيئه",
                    "answer_2": "العلاقات ",
                    "answer_3": "الحدود ",
                    "correct_answer": " نظام مرن "
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": "من خصائص النظام",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "يتصف بالشمول",
                    "answer_2": "نظام هادف",
                    "answer_3": "عمليه مستمره",
                    "correct_answer": "جميع الاجابات صحيحه"
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "من وظائف الاداره",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "الانتاج",
                    "answer_2": "التسويق",
                    "answer_3": "التمويل",
                    "correct_answer": "التخطيط"
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "كبر حجم المنظمات واتساع نطاق الاسواق والاعمال والتطور التكنولوجي من ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "وظائف نظم المعلومات",
                    "answer_2": "محددات النجاح",
                    "answer_3": "العوامل المؤثره علي النظام",
                    "correct_answer": "اسباب الحاجه للنظام"
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": "هو نظام متكامل يتكون من مجموعه من الاجزاء وذلك بغرض تزويد الاداره بكافه المعلومات لكل ماتحتاجه من المعلومات عن الوظائف والانشطه و تقديمها لمتخذ القرار ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "نظم دعم القرار",
                    "answer_2": "نظم دعم المعلومات الانتاجيه",
                    "answer_3": "نظم المعلومات التسويقيه ",
                    "correct_answer": " نظم المعلومات  الاداريه"
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": "من محددات نظم نجاح نظم المعلومات ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "الافراد",
                    "answer_2": "الاجهزه",
                    "answer_3": "البرمجيات ",
                    "correct_answer": "جميع الاجابات صحيحه"
                }
            },
            "ten": {
                "question": "هي برمجيات تشتغل لتنظيم المعلومات ومن امثلتها ترتيب البيانات",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "جميع الاجابات صحيحه",
                    "answer_2": "برمجيات الموارد",
                    "answer_3": "برمجيات التطبيقات ",
                    "correct_answer": "برمجيات النظم"
                }
            },
            "eleven": {
                "question": " برنامج الاجور يعتبر من البرمجيات ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " النظم",
                    "answer_2": " الموراد",
                    "answer_3": " التسويق ",
                    "correct_answer": " التطبيقات "
                }
            },
            "twelve": {
                "question": "   من العوامل المؤثره علي نظام المعلومات  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " المعرفه",
                    "answer_2": " الاجهزه",
                    "answer_3": " قواعد البيانات ",
                    "correct_answer": " العولمه "
                }
            },
            "thrteen": {
                "question": " هي عباره عن معلومات تم تجميعها وتنظيمها وتحويلها الي خبره تنظيميه   ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " البيانات",
                    "answer_2": " العمليات",
                    "answer_3": " التغذيه العكسيه ",
                    "correct_answer": " المعرفه "
                }
            },
            "fourteen": {
                "question": "   تجميع وتصميم ومعالجه ونقل واسترجاع البيانات والمعلومات  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " الاداره الالكترونيه",
                    "answer_2": " الاختراق الالكتروني",
                    "answer_3": " البيئه ",
                    "correct_answer": " تكنولوجيا المعلومات "
                }

            }

        },
        "الجزء التاني من الامتحان": {
            "one": {
                "question": "من المزايا المترتبه علي تكنولوجيا المعلومات كل مايلي ماعدا",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " تذليل الصعوبات ",
                    "answer_2": " فصل العمل ",
                    "answer_3": " الغاء الحدود ",
                    "correct_answer": " انه وسيله من وسائل التطور "
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": " تعتبر من اخطر المخاطر وذلك لانه علي علم بكافه مخرجات النظام ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " المخاطر الخارجيه ",
                    "answer_2": " مخاطر القرصنه ",
                    "answer_3": " مخاطر طبيعيه ",
                    "correct_answer": " المخاطر الداخليه "
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": " يعتبر هم المصدر الرئيسي للمخاطر ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " مديرين المنظمه ",
                    "answer_2": " محاسبين المنظمه ",
                    "answer_3": " سائقين المنظمه ",
                    "correct_answer": " موظفي المنظمه "
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": " هي مخاطر تحدث نتيجه السهو والنسيان ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " مخاطر طبيعيه ",
                    "answer_2": " القرصنه ",
                    "answer_3": " متعمده ",
                    "correct_answer": " غير متعمده "
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": " هي عمليه غير شرعيه تتم عن طريق استغلال نقاط الضعف علي النظام ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " تكنولوجيا المعلومات ",
                    "answer_2": " الاداره الالكترونيه ",
                    "answer_3": " مدير النظام ",
                    "correct_answer": " الاختراق التكنولوجي "
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": " مسؤوليه حمايه النظام المعلوماتي علي  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " المبرمج ",
                    "answer_2": " المصمم ",
                    "answer_3": " رئيس المنظمه ",
                    "correct_answer": " مدير النظام "
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": " هو شخص يقوم بعمليه الاختراق ويطلق عليه من المبرمجين ولكنه ليس لديه النيه في الحاق الضرر",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " الهاكر ",
                    "answer_2": " الهاكر الاسود ",
                    "answer_3": " جميع ماسبق ",
                    "correct_answer": " الكراكر "
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": " من دوافع عمليه الاختراق ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " حرب الوكاله ",
                    "answer_2": " ماديه  ",
                    "answer_3": " التجسس علي البريد ",
                    "correct_answer": " جميع ماسبق "
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": " من طرق الاختراق التكنولوجي كل مايلي ماعدا  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " الماسنجر ",
                    "answer_2": " الثغرات  ",
                    "answer_3": " الفيروسات ",
                    "correct_answer": " ليس مما سبق "
                }
            },
            "ten": {
                "question": " من طرق الحمايه من الاختراق الالكتروني  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " عمل قائمه بالمواقع ",
                    "answer_2": " عمل المسح الدوري  ",
                    "answer_3": " تخصيص نظام للاجهزه ",
                    "correct_answer": " جميع الاجابات صحيحه "
                }
            },
            "eleven": {
                "question": " هو نظام تفاعلي يهدف الي مساعده متخذ القرار من خلال توفير البيانات والاحصاءات والمعلومات لتحويلهم الي معلومات سهله الفهم ومتخذ القرار ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " نظم المعلومات الاداريه ",
                    "answer_2": " نظم المعلومات الانتاجيه  ",
                    "answer_3": " نظم المعلومات التسويقيه ",
                    "correct_answer": " نظم دعم القرار "
                }
            },
            "twelve": {
                "question": " هو ناتج عمليه المفاضله بين البدائل المطروحه ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " الدعم  ",
                    "answer_2": " النظم ",
                    "answer_3": " البديل ",
                    "correct_answer": " القرار "
                }
            },
            "thrteen": {
                "question": " هي قرارات ذات طبيعه روتينيه لا تحتاج الي معالجه  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " القرارات غير المبرمجه  ",
                    "answer_2": " القرارات نصف المبرمجه ",
                    "answer_3": " القرارات الاستراتيجيه ",
                    "correct_answer": " القرارات المبرمجه "
                }
            },
            "fourteen": {
                "question": " هي قرارات رسم السياسات وتقوم بها الاداره العليا  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " القرارات التشغيليه  ",
                    "answer_2": " القرارات الاداريه  ",
                    "answer_3": " القرارات التنفيذيه ",
                    "correct_answer": " القرارات الاستراتيجيه "
                }
            }
        },
        "صح و خطا": {
            "one": {
                "question": " تكامل المعلومه هي المده الفاصله بين انتاج المعلومه ومده الحصول عليها  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": " البعد الزمني يصف الفتره الزمنيه التي تتعلق بالمعلومه ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " خطا ",
                    "correct_answer": " صح "
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": " كلما كان المصدر اكثر ثقه قلت قيمه المعلومه  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا  "
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": " المصمم هو المسؤول عم بناء قاعده البيانات ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": " الحقول هي مجموعه من السجلات  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": " خبره متخذ القرار لاتؤثر علي النظام ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "  صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": " الاستقلاليه بالخصوصيه من خصائص البيانات ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " غلط ",
                    "correct_answer": " صح "
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": " الدقه والصدق صفات بعد المحتوي ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " غلط ",
                    "correct_answer": " صح "
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": " مدير قاعده البيانات هو الذي يقوم باداره قواعد البيانات ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " غلط ",
                    "correct_answer": " صح "
                }
            },
            "ten": {
                "question": " الامان والحمايه من العوامل المؤثره علي النظام ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " غلط ",
                    "correct_answer": " صح "
                }
            },
            "eleven": {
                "question": " المنظمه تعتبر نظام فرعي مغلق ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "twelve": {
                "question": " التغذيه العكسيه هي ردود الافعال السلبيه والايجابيه لمدخلات ومخرجات النظام ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "thrteen": {
                "question": " المخرجات هي ردود الافعال الناتجه عن مدخلات النظام  ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            },
            "fourteen": {
                "question": " بيانات الموظفين وبيانات العمليات الاداريه من مدخلات نظم المعلومات التسويقيه ",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": " صح ",
                    "correct_answer": " خطا "
                }
            }
        },
        "react js": {
            "one": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "ten": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "eleven": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "twelve": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "thrteen": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "fourteen": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            }
        },
        "front-end": {
            "one": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "ten": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "eleven": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "twelve": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "thrteen": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "fourteen": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            }
        },
        "git": {
            "one": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "ten": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "eleven": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "twelve": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "thrteen": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            },
            "fourteen": {
                "question": "",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "",
                    "answer_2": "",
                    "answer_3": "",
                    "correct_answer": ""
                }
            }
        }
    }
}]"answer_2": "float",
                    "answer_3": "value",
                    "correct_answer": "number"
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "Which property references the DOM object that dispatched an event?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "self",
                    "answer_2": "object",
                    "answer_3": "source",
                    "correct_answer": "target"
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": "When would you use a conditional statement?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "When you want to reuse a set of statements multiple times.",
                    "answer_2": "When you want to group data together.",
                    "answer_3": "When you want to loop through a group of statement.",
                    "correct_answer": "When you want your code to choose between multiple options"
                }
            },
            "nine": {
                "question": "Which Object method returns an iterable that can be used to iterate over the properties of an object?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "Object.each()",
                    "answer_2": "Object.loop()",
                    "answer_3": "Object.get()",
                    "correct_answer": "Object.keys()"
                }
            }
        },
        "react js": {
            "one": {
                "question": "If you want to import just the Component from the React library, what syntax do you use?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "import React.Component from 'react'",
                    "answer_2": "import [ Component ] from 'react'",
                    "answer_3": "import Component from 'react'",
                    "correct_answer": "import { Component } from 'react'"
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "import React.Component from 'react'",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "Mocha",
                    "answer_2": "Chai",
                    "answer_3": "Sinon",
                    "correct_answer": "Jest"
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "How do you handle passing through the component tree without having to pass props down manually at every level?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "React Router",
                    "answer_2": "React Pinpoint",
                    "answer_3": "React Router",
                    "correct_answer": "React Context"
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": "Why might you use useReducer over useState in a React component?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "when you want to replace Redux",
                    "answer_2": "when you want to break your production app",
                    "answer_3": "when you want to improve performance",
                    "correct_answer": "when you need to manage more complex state in an app"
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": "What can you use to handle code splitting?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "React.memo",
                    "answer_2": "React.split",
                    "answer_3": "React.fallback",
                    "correct_answer": "React.lazy"
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "What is the children prop?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "a property that lets you set an array as a property",
                    "answer_2": "a property that lets you pass components as data to other components",
                    "answer_3": "a property that adds child components to state",
                    "correct_answer": "a property that lets you pass data to child elements"
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "Which attribute do you use to replace innerHTML in the browser DOM?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "injectHTML",
                    "answer_2": "weirdSetInnerHTML",
                    "answer_3": "strangeHTML",
                    "correct_answer": "dangerouslySetInnerHTML"
                }
            }
        },
        "front-end": {
            "one": {
                "question": "Variables declared with the let keyword have what type of scope?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "function scope",
                    "answer_2": "inline scope",
                    "answer_3": "global scope",
                    "correct_answer": "block scope"
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "Which attribute must have a unique value each time it is used in an HTML document?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "title",
                    "answer_2": "class",
                    "answer_3": "style",
                    "correct_answer": "id"
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "Which CSS property will not trigger layout recalculation?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "top",
                    "answer_2": "width",
                    "answer_3": "height",
                    "correct_answer": "opacity"
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": "What does the === comparison operator do?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "It sets one variable equal to another in both value and type",
                    "answer_2": "It tests for equality of type only",
                    "answer_3": "It tests for equality of value only",
                    "correct_answer": "It tests for equality of value and type"
                }
            },
            "five": {
                "question": "What is the <label> element used for?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "to identify the difference parts of a figure",
                    "answer_2": "as a caption for images",
                    "answer_3": "as a heading for tables",
                    "correct_answer": "to explain what needs to be entered into a form field"
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "The browser finds some CSS that it does not understand. What is likely happen?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "The page will not display",
                    "answer_2": "An error message will be displayed",
                    "answer_3": "The browser will not load the stylesheet",
                    "correct_answer": "The browser will ignore the unknown CSS"
                }
            },
            "seven": {
                "question": "Which choice is not a value of the type attribute of the <input> element?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "range",
                    "answer_2": "date",
                    "answer_3": "password",
                    "correct_answer": "address"
                }
            },
            "eight": {
                "question": "Which part of the URL https://app.uniswap.org/pool specifies the domain name",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "https",
                    "answer_2": "org",
                    "answer_3": "uniswap.org",
                    "correct_answer": "app.uniswap"
                }
            }
        },
        "git": {
            "one": {
                "question": "How can you check your current git version?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "git --v",
                    "answer_2": "git --current",
                    "answer_3": "git --option",
                    "correct_answer": "git --version"
                }
            },
            "two": {
                "question": "What command lets you create a connection between a local and remote repository?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "git remote add new",
                    "answer_2": "git remote new origin",
                    "answer_3": "git remote origin",
                    "correct_answer": "git remote add origin"
                }
            },
            "three": {
                "question": "What option can you use to apply git configurations across your entire git environment?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "--master",
                    "answer_2": "--all",
                    "answer_3": "--master",
                    "correct_answer": "--global"
                }
            },
            "four": {
                "question": "Where are files stored before they are committed to the local repository?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "Saved files",
                    "answer_2": "git documents",
                    "answer_3": "git cache",
                    "correct_answer": "Staging area"
                }
            },
            "six": {
                "question": "What command would let you modify your previous commit?",
                "answers": {
                    "answer_1": "--modify",
                    "answer_2": "--quickfix",
                    "answer_3": "--fix",
                    "correct_answer": "--amend"
                }
            }
        }
    }
}]
